zamzata.com 2011-06-04

# Zamzata Privacy Policy

Zamzata’s policy is to protect your personal information when signing up as a user.  Until you sign up as a user, you may browse our site without revealing your personal information.  By accepting the privacy policy and user agreement you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information.  The information will include collecting your email address, your activities performed on our site, shipping and billing information, discussions in forums and chats, and computer sign in data. The purpose for us collecting this information is to help our customer service and make your visit at Zamzata a pleasant experience, while preventing potentially illegal activities.

Zamzata may use your personal information in different circumstances.   This could be when there is a legal requirement to do so through law enforcement for an illegal activity.    It may be used to resolve disputes, for promotional purposes, or other third parties. 

Zamzata encourages you to share personal and financial information to complete transactions.  We cannot guarantee the security of your information when dealing with another user.  You must use your discretion when dealing with other users before entering a transaction.  When you obtain personal information of another user during a transaction you may only use that email address and financial information for that transaction, and not for unsolicited commercial interests.

Zamzata uses cookies on our site to help with our customer service.  You are free to decline our use of cookies if your browser permits, but it may interfere with the use of our site.

Zamzata will not allow the use of spam on our community of users.  You may not use another user’s email address, discussion boards, or posting for spam purposes. 

Third party hackers in the past have unlawfully intercepted private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Zamzata. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.   

Zamzata has the right at anytime to amend this Privacy Policy without giving prior notice to the users.
